<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Joe Miller</title>
    <link>http://joemiller.me/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Joe Miller</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 07:50:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://joemiller.me/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Signing releases with a project GPG key</title>
      <link>http://joemiller.me/2019/07/signing-releases-with-a-project-gpg-key/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 07:50:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joemiller.me/2019/07/signing-releases-with-a-project-gpg-key/</guid>
      <description>Intro This article presents a step-by-step guide for signing a project&amp;rsquo;s releases with GPG. It came from my own experience of adding GPG-signing support to vault-token-helper.
Why sign releases? The Apache Foundation has an excellent explanatino already so I&amp;rsquo;ll just borrow theirs: why
 A signature allows anyone to verify that a file is identical to the one created by the Apache release manager. Using a signature:
 users can make sure that what they received has not been modified in any way, either accidentally via a faulty transmission channel, or intentionally (with or without malicious intent)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retired Old Blog Posts, Migrated to Hugo and Github Pages</title>
      <link>http://joemiller.me/2019/07/retired-old-blog-posts-migrated-to-hugo-and-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 12:06:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joemiller.me/2019/07/retired-old-blog-posts-migrated-to-hugo-and-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>This blog sat idle for 5 years, the last post was 2014. Old posts have been un-published from the site but are still available in the github repo.
In addition to retiring old posts the blog was migrated from jekyll to hugo. Hosting is now a combination of Github Pages + Cloudflare (previously S3 + Cloudflare). With Circle-CI deploying on master merges.
There may be a few posts going forward. We&amp;rsquo;ll see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heroku log drains into Logstash</title>
      <link>http://joemiller.me/2014/01/heroku-log-drains-into-logstash/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 11:45:58 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joemiller.me/2014/01/heroku-log-drains-into-logstash/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The first and obvious option for shipping logs from a heroku app to Logstash is the &lt;a href=&#34;http://logstash.net/docs/1.3.3/inputs/heroku&#34;&gt;heroku input plugin&lt;/a&gt;. However, this requires installing the Heroku gem and deploying the login + password of a Heroku user to your Logstash server(s). At this time it seems that any user given permissions to an app on Heroku has full control. Not good when you just want to fetch logs. Heroku has added more granular permissions via OAuth but the Heroku gem does not support OAuth tokens yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately there&amp;rsquo;s another option using Heroku&amp;rsquo;s log drain. Setting up a log drain from Heroku to Logstash is almost as simple as the Heroku input plugin but has the major advantage of not requiring any new users or passwords to be deployed on the Logstash server.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of statsd server implementations</title>
      <link>http://joemiller.me/2011/09/list-of-statsd-server-implementations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 11:34:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joemiller.me/2011/09/list-of-statsd-server-implementations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Statsd is a simple client/server mechanism from the folks at Etsy that allows operations and development teams to easily feed a variety of metrics into a Graphite system. For more info on statsd read the seminal blog article on Statsd &lt;a href=&#34;http://codeascraft.etsy.com/2011/02/15/measure-anything-measure-everything/&#34; title=&#34;Etsy: Measure Anything, Measure Everything&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Measure Anything, Measure Everything&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>